Hello
안녕하세요
I am Yamashita
I am Yamashita
Lloyd Road in five minutes
5분만에 로이드 로드
The phone booth opposite Tai Sheng Leather Store
Tai Sheng Leather Store 맞은편 전화부스
if late
늦으면
cancel transaction
거래 취소
keep up
유지하다
I have arrived
나는 도착했다
Can it be traded?
거래가 가능한가요?
Luban Road seven minutes later
7분후 루반로
if late
늦으면
cancel transaction
거래 취소
What tricks are you doing?
당신은 어떤 트릭을하고 있습니까?
you
너
Lu Ban Road
루반로드
okay
좋아요
Sit tight
꽉 앉아
quick
빠른
Over here, you two
저기, 너희 둘
Over there
저기
Walk
걷다
Yamashita Takeo must want to know
야마시타 다케오가 알고 싶어할 것 같아요
Who are they trading with?
그들은 누구와 거래하고 있나요?
Whether it's his men or himself
그 사람이건 그 자신이건 간에
There will definitely be an ambush set up.
분명히 매복 준비가 있을 것입니다.
As long as we get the box
우리가 상자를 얻는 한
He will definitely find a way to follow
그 사람은 분명 따라갈 방법을 찾을 거야
I keep changing the place where I trade
거래하는 곳이 계속 바뀌네요
Just want to get rid of the people they are following and ambushing.
그들이 따르고 매복하고 있는 사람들을 제거하고 싶을 뿐입니다.
Then you can't get rid of it
그러면 헤어나올 수 없어
That's when it's time for you to play
그때가 바로 네가 놀 시간이야
Brother, your plan is good.
형제여, 당신의 계획은 좋습니다.
but your last call
그런데 마지막 통화
Call the phone booth on Luban Road
Luban Road에 있는 전화부스에 전화하세요
Around 3:10 p.m.
오후 3시 10분쯤
Why
왜
parking
주차
good
좋은
How many places do you want me to run?
내가 얼마나 많은 곳을 달리기를 원하시나요?
You'll be out of the phone booth later
넌 나중에 전화 부스에서 나올 거야
A rickshaw will pass by
인력거가 지나갈 거예요
You threw your stuff in the back of the rickshaw
인력거 뒤에 물건을 던졌잖아
You fooled me for a long time
당신은 오랫동안 나를 속였습니다
When will you give me the recipe?
레시피는 언제 알려주실 건가요?
Wait until I confirm the number of gold bars
내가 금괴 개수를 확인할 때까지 기다려 주세요.
nature will give it to you
자연이 당신에게 그것을 줄 것입니다
besides
게다가
six o'clock
여섯시
Keep waiting for my news in this phone booth
이 전화부스에서 내 소식을 계속 기다려줘
Why should I believe you?
내가 왜 당신을 믿어야합니까?
Gold bars are given to you
금괴가 당신에게 주어집니다
What should I do if the recipe is not given to me?
레시피가 주어지지 않으면 어떻게 해야 하나요?
You can choose not to believe me
당신은 내 말을 믿지 않기로 선택할 수 있습니다
but i think
하지만 나는 생각해
you have no other choice
너에겐 다른 선택의 여지가 없어
good
좋은
I trust you
나는 당신을 신뢰합니다
But I don't have time to wait for you anymore
하지만 더 이상 당신을 기다릴 시간이 없어요
You'll call later
나중에 전화할게
To Kikukawa Japanese Store
To Kikukawa Korean Store
good
좋은
knew
알고 있었다
we were fooled
우리는 속았다
Turn around from Luban Road and you'll find Nongshanxi Road.
Luban Road에서 돌아서면 Nongshanxi Road가 나옵니다.
At ten minutes past three in the afternoon
오후 3시 10분
That was when Tongxing Automobile Dealers changed shifts.
그때 Tongxing Automobile Dealers가 교대 근무를 변경했습니다.
There are many cars there
거기 차가 많아요
It's useless to clean it up
닦아봐도 소용없어
OK OK OK
오케이 오케이 오케이
Chinese gold
중국 금
It should be returned to the hands of the Chinese
중국 손에 돌려줘야 한다
Do you think so?
그렇게 생각?
okay
좋아요
Stop biting
그만 물어뜯어
Count quickly
빠르게 계산
Check if the number is correct
번호가 맞는지 확인해보세요
Don't blame me then
그럼 나를 비난하지 마세요
I forgive him for not daring to lose one.
감히 하나도 잃지 않은 그를 용서합니다.
counting
계산
You said you made the mountain go round and round
당신은 산을 빙빙 돌게 만들었다고 하더군요
Can you give him what he wants?
그가 원하는 것을 줄 수 있나요?
Do you want to give it or not?
주고 싶나요, 안 주고 싶나요?
Even though I wouldn’t expect to be beaten to death at the foot of this mountain,
이 산기슭에서 맞아죽을 거라고는 상상도 못했는데,
It was you who made the deal with him
그 사람과 거래한 건 바로 너였어
But if he can't get the formula
하지만 그가 공식을 얻을 수 없다면
Mobilize troops to investigate
조사를 위해 군대를 동원하라
No matter what happens, this will be traced to us, right?
무슨 일이 있어도 이건 우리한테 추적이 되겠죠?
But forget it
하지만 잊어버려
It’s better not to give it
안주는게 낫지
otherwise
그렇지 않으면
Go! Go! Go
가다! 가다! 가다
Otherwise, you have to ask me to deliver it again.
그렇지 않으면 다시 배달해달라고 요청하셔야 합니다.
four or five
4개 아니면 5개
Doing business
사업을 하는 중
Money and goods settled
돈과 물건이 정산됨
eight
여덟
I actually have no use for this edge paper recipe.
실제로 이 가장자리 종이 레시피는 쓸모가 없습니다.
so
그래서
Leave it to Colonel Yamashita for me
야마시타 대령에게 맡겨주세요
You still have to give it away, right?
그래도 줘야지, 그렇지?
Where to send
보낼 곳
Xiafei Road
샤페이 로드
There is a phone booth on Xiafei Road
Xiafei Road에 전화 부스가 있습니다.
six o'clock
여섯시
I'll call the Kikukawa Japanese Store
키쿠카와 일본매장에 전화할게요
You put this thing away before six o'clock
6시가 되기 전에 이걸 치워두세요
Put it behind the phone in the phone booth
공중전화부스 전화기 뒤에 놓아두세요
Remember
기억하다
You have to leave quickly before six o'clock
6시 이전에는 빨리 나가야 해요
Kikukawa Japanese Store
Kikukawa Japanese Store
right
오른쪽
that time
그때
He should be with his fiancée
그는 약혼자와 함께 있어야 해
OK OK OK
오케이 오케이 오케이
I see
알겠어요
Don't move
움직이지 마세요
Don't you believe me?
당신은 나를 믿지 않습니까?
I believe
나는 믿는다
How much do you believe in me?
당신은 나를 얼마나 믿나요?
How much do I trust you
나는 당신을 얼마나 신뢰합니까?
How about it
어때요?
Proceed as originally planned
당초 계획대로 진행
The handwriting is obviously different
필체가 확실히 다르네요
The raw materials and proportions written are also different.
쓰여진 원재료와 비율도 다릅니다.
This recipe is fake
이 레시피는 가짜입니다
Luo Guanqun is testing me
Luo Guanqun이 나를 시험하고 있습니다
Hello
안녕하세요
Mr. Yamashita
Mr. Yamashita
welcome
환영
Where is the cold dew?
차가운 이슬은 어디에 있습니까?
Hanlu is accompanied by her friends
한루는 친구들과 함께
Are you trying on a kimono over there?
저기서 기모노를 입어보고 계시나요?
The small cloth bag given to me by Luo Guanqun
나관쿤이 나에게 준 작은 천 가방
Put it behind the phone booth on Xiafei Road
Xiafei Road의 전화 부스 뒤에 두세요.
It will eventually come back to him
결국 그 사람한테 다시 돌아오겠지
At that time, if the formula inside
그때 안에 수식을 넣으면
Not the one he put in
그 사람이 넣은 건 아니고
This proves that I was the one who changed the formula.
이는 공식을 바꾼 사람이 바로 나라는 것을 증명한다.
Luo Guanqun must have the real formula
Luo Guanqun은 진짜 공식을 가지고 있어야합니다
Put it somewhere else
다른 곳에 두세요
He will call Yamashita at six o'clock
그는 6시에 야마시타에게 전화할 것이다
tell him where the recipe is
그에게 레시피가 어디 있는지 말해줘
That's my last chance too
나도 그게 마지막 기회야
Mr. Yamashita
Mr. Yamashita
Come and see
와서 봐
Miss Hanlu’s temperament is graceful and luxurious
한루씨의 기질은 우아하고 고급스럽습니다
so
그래서
I specially chose the royal style with brocade
특별히 브로케이드로 왕실 스타일을 선택했습니다
How about it
어때요?
beautiful
아름다운
So beautiful
너무 아름다워
I'm so embarrassed by your praise
당신의 칭찬에 너무 부끄러워요
I also think this outfit is too gorgeous.
저도 이 의상이 너무 예쁜 것 같아요.
Hello, what can I do for you?
안녕하세요. 무엇을 도와드릴까요?
wedding time
결혼식 시간
I will also wear a horn
나도 경적을 달겠다
yes
예
Miss Zuo
미스 주오
It's your phone number
네 전화번호야
It’s Higashida-kun, the owner of the Japanese confectionery shop.
화과자점 주인인 히가시다군이에요.
I'll just pick it up
그냥 가져갈게요
good
좋은
Hello
안녕하세요
Hey it's me
이봐 나야
It's Higashikata-kun
It's Higashikata-kun
Hello
안녕하세요
at six o'clock
여섯시에
Yamashita will receive a call
야마시타가 전화를 받을 거야
The phone will tell Yamashita an address.
전화가 야마시타에게 주소를 알려줄 것입니다.
You and Hanlu must find a way
당신과 한루는 방법을 찾아야 합니다
Get this address
이 주소를 받으세요
i want to be at the wedding
나는 결혼식에 참석하고 싶어
Prepare Japanese snacks for guests
손님을 위한 일본식 간식을 준비하세요
Zuo Shuangtao helped me contact this company
Zuo Shuangtao가 이 회사에 연락하는 데 도움을 주었습니다.
They were anxious to decide on the types and styles of dim sum.
그들은 딤섬의 종류와 스타일을 결정하는데 고민을 많이 했습니다.
I asked them to call here.
여기로 전화해 달라고 했어요.
I've made you worry about it
내가 널 걱정하게 만들었어
should
~해야 한다
You mean water yokan?
물양갱 말인가요?
Is Mohagi the best?
모하기가 최고야?
yes
예
all I want
내가 원하는 모든 것
be safe
안전한
OK
좋아요
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
Hello
안녕하세요
two knives
두 개의 칼
Find a few people to pretend to be debt collectors
채권추심자 행세를 할 사람을 몇 명 찾아보세요
Go to Gujialong No. 32 at six o'clock
6시 구자룡32번으로 이동
Debt collector
채권추심자
No need to pretend
척할 필요 없어
I know a lot of them
나는 그들 중 많은 것을 알고 있습니다.
This Higashikata-kun
This Higashikata-kun
It’s so verbose
???너무 장황하다
But I've explained everything
하지만 난 다 설명했어
Thanks to you
고마워
Otherwise there are so many things
안 그러면 일이 너무 많아서
I really can't take care of it by myself
나 혼자서는 정말 감당이 안 돼
Miss Hanlu
미스 한루
I picked out a Hakata belt for you
당신을 위해 하카타 벨트를 골랐습니다
I think it would look better with it
그걸로 하면 더 좋을 것 같아요
How about we try again
우리 다시 해보는 건 어때?
What do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
Then I'll try
그럼 나도 해볼게
give it to me
그걸 나에게주세요
I'll just come
그냥 올게
I'll get a call at six o'clock
6시에 전화할게
The phone will tell Yamashita an address.
전화가 야마시타에게 주소를 알려줄 것입니다.
We have to get the address first
먼저 주소를 알아내야 해요
then what should i do
그럼 난 어떻게 해야 해?
take it easy
진정해
Do everything as I say
내가 말한 대로 다 해라
cold dew
차가운 이슬
It's getting late today
오늘은 늦어지고 있어
This halo brocade kimono you tried on
당신이 입어본 후광단단 기모노
It's settled
해결됐어
correct
옳은
I'm here to choose a kimono for me today.
오늘은 나를 위한 기모노를 고르러 왔습니다.
I haven’t picked out a set for you yet.
나는 아직 당신을 위한 세트를 고르지 않았습니다.
I'm in no hurry
난 서두르지 않아
Today I mainly want to help you try it out
오늘은 주로 여러분이 시도해 볼 수 있도록 도와드리고 싶습니다.
Another six o'clock
또 6시
I have one more thing to do
나 할 일이 하나 더 있어
six o'clock
여섯시
It's only half past five
다섯시 반밖에 안 됐는데
There's enough time
시간은 충분해요
when you are not around
당신이 주변에 없을 때
Shuangtao and I helped you choose a set
Shuangtao와 제가 세트 선택을 도와드렸습니다
You go and try it
가서 한번 해보세요
It was carefully selected by Miss Hanlu
미스한루가 엄선한
Weft brocade pattern with feather woven hakama
깃털로 엮은 하카마 위사 비단 패턴
I'll get it
내가 갖겠다
Just try it
그냥 시도 해 봐
people
사람들
I also want to see you as a groom.
저도 신랑으로 뵙고 싶습니다.
OK
좋아요
good
좋은
Brought it
가져왔어
go try
가서 시도해봐
Manager Luo
루오 매니저
How about it
어때요?
got it
알았어요
come and see
와서 봐
How about it
어때요?
He didn't change it either
그 사람도 바꾸지 않았어
Didn't you change it?
바꾸지 않았나요?
Where is it?
어디입니까?
Just these brothers
바로 이 형제들
This debt-ridden gambler
이 빚쟁이 도박꾼
Just upstairs here
여기 바로 위층에 있어요
gambler
노름꾼
come down
내려와
Debtful gambler, come down
빚진 도박꾼이여, 내려와라
Who is it?
누구입니까?
Come down quickly
빨리 내려와
cold dew
차가운 이슬
How about it
어때요?
Why is it so different from what I thought?
내가 생각한거랑 왜이렇게 다른거지?
Zuo Shuangtao, what do you think?
Zuo Shuangtao, 어떻게 생각하세요?
may be
아마도
Is it a problem with the fabric?
원단에 문제가 있는 걸까요?
Too soft
너무 부드럽다
I didn’t mention Mr. Yamashita’s physical characteristics
야마시타 씨의 신체적 특성에 대해서는 언급하지 않았습니다.
show it
보여
I think it's okay
내 생각엔 괜찮은 것 같아
correct
옳은
Do you remember the other set we chose?
우리가 선택한 다른 세트를 기억하시나요?
right
오른쪽
It's brocade woven fabric
브로케이드 직조 원단이에요
That one is stiffer
저쪽이 더 딱딱해요
Might be more suitable for Mr. Yamashita
야마시타 씨에게 더 적합할지도 모릅니다
I'll take it
내가 할게요
good
좋은
Hurry up
서둘러요
Wedding is a major event in a woman's life
결혼식은 여성의 일생에 있어서 가장 중요한 사건이다
every detail
모든 세부 사항
It has to be perfect
완벽해야 해
Don't be impatient
조급해하지 마세요
How could I be impatient?
내가 어떻게 참을성이 없겠는가?
good
좋은
I will try until you are satisfied
만족하실 때까지 노력하겠습니다
Gamblers, come out now
도박꾼들아 이제 나와라
come down
내려와
leave them alone
그들을 내버려 둬
Come down and pay back the money
내려와서 돈을 갚으세요
come down
내려와
The clothes are here
옷은 여기 있어요
Go and try it
가서 시도해 보세요
You have something else to do later
나중에 또 할 일이 있잖아
Go quickly
빨리 가세요
It should be Higashida-kun
히가시다군이겠지
He just asked me about your taste preferences
그 사람이 방금 나한테 네 취향을 물어봤어
I really don't know
난 정말 모르겠어요
I'm sorry to bother you
당신을 귀찮게해서 미안 해요
Miss Hanlu
미스 한루
Go pick it up
가서 가져가세요
good
좋은
I'll answer the phone
전화 받겠습니다
Go try it quickly
빨리 가서 먹어봐
Hello
안녕하세요
Is it Higashida-kun?
Is it Higashida-kun?
Is this the Kikukawa Japanese Store?
여기가 키쿠카와 일본 상점인가요?
yes
예
I'm looking for Mr. Yamashita
야마시타 씨를 찾고 있어요
open the door open the door
문을 열어라 문을 열어라
open the door
문을 열어라
Mr. Yamashita is trying on clothes
야마시타 씨가 옷을 입어보고 있습니다
Who are you
누구세요
I made an appointment with Yamashita
야마시타와 약속을 잡았어
what are you doing
뭐하세요
Drive them away
그들을 몰아내세요
You are sick
당신은 아픈
Are you going to attract the police?
경찰을 끌어들일 건가요?
He was trying on a kimono
그는 기모노를 입어보고 있었다
There are also various accessories
다양한 악세사리도 있어요
It might take a while
시간이 좀 걸릴 수도 있어요
How about you call back later?
나중에 다시 전화하는 게 어때요?
can you make him hurry up
그 사람을 서두르게 해줄 수 있어?
come down
내려와
Pay back the money
돈을 갚으세요
Did you hear that?
그거 들었어?
hurry up
서둘러요
Are you okay at the foot of the mountain?
산기슭에는 괜찮나요?
The police are coming
경찰이 오고 있어요
The police are coming, go quickly
경찰이 온다 빨리 가
stop
멈추다
Go quickly
빨리 가세요
Don't run
뛰지 마세요
stop
멈추다
You tell him I can't wait any longer
당신은 그에게 내가 더 이상 기다릴 수 없다고 말해요
The location is Sanguantang Road
위치는 싼관탕루(Sanguantang Road)에 있습니다.
The sixth telephone pole from west to east
서쪽에서 동쪽으로 여섯 번째 전신주
The phone booth opposite
맞은편에 있는 공중전화부스
There's something behind the phone
전화기 뒤에 뭔가가 있어요
have you understood
이해했니?
good
좋은
I wrote it down
적어놨어요
I'll tell him
내가 그에게 말할게
Go quickly
빨리 가세요
Hello Higashida-kun
Hello Higashida-kun
Miss Hanlu
미스 한루
How about it
어때요?
Did Yamashita doubt you?
야마시타가 당신을 의심했나요?
Ge Ying doesn’t have it
Ge Ying은 그것을 가지고 있지 않습니다
Then replace it with a big fortune roll
그런 다음 큰 포춘 롤로 교체하세요.
Don't eat these common people's snacks
이런 서민 간식 먹지 마세요
Mr. Yamashita will be unhappy
야마시타 씨는 기분이 안 좋을 거예요
Mr. Yamashita
Mr. Yamashita
according to tradition
전통에 따르면
The wedding kimono must be matched with a haori
결혼식 기모노는 하오리와 매치되어야 합니다
Yamashita-kun
야마시타 군
This is the last one
이게 마지막이야
Go try it quickly
빨리 가서 먹어봐
quickly
빠르게
Sanguantang Road from west to east
서쪽에서 동쪽으로 삼관당로(Sanguantang Road)
The phone booth next to the sixth telephone pole
6번 전신주 옆 전화부스
There's something behind the phone
전화기 뒤에 뭔가가 있어요
good
좋은
But I have to get there before going down the mountain
하지만 산을 내려가기 전에 거기에 도착해야 해요
But where I am now
하지만 지금 내가 있는 곳은
Compared to Japanese stores
일본 매장에 비해
Further away from Sanguantang Road
Sanguantang Road에서 더 멀리 떨어져 있습니다.
You must find a way to help me drag me down the mountain
나를 산 아래로 끌고 내려가는 데 도움을 줄 방법을 찾아야 해요
good
좋은
Miss Hanlu
미스 한루
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Chen Jiaping asked us to drag Shanxia down
Chen Jiaping은 우리에게 Shanxia를 끌어 내려달라고 요청했습니다.
Miss Hanlu
미스 한루
When walking in kimono, you have to take small steps.
기모노를 입고 걸을 때는 작은 걸음으로 걸어야 합니다.
yes
예
Look, I almost fell down
봐, 나 넘어질 뻔했어
This brocade-embellished kimono is paired with a haori
이 브로케이드 장식 기모노는 하오리와 짝을 이룹니다.
It's really extraordinary
정말 대단해요
Zuo Shuangtao, what do you think?
Zuo Shuangtao, 어떻게 생각하세요?
I think so
그렇게 생각해요
This outfit really looks like Mr. Yamashita
이 의상 정말 야마시타씨 닮았네요
More tall and stalwart
키가 더 크고 튼튼해요
correct
옳은
Why did the phone ring twice just now?
방금 전화벨이 두 번 울린 이유는 무엇입니까?
After answering Dongtian's call,
Dongtian의 전화를 받은 후,
I picked up another one
나는 또 하나를 골랐다
Who are you looking for?
당신은 누구를 찾고 있나요?
looking for you
당신을 찾고
Looking for me
나를 찾고 있어요
Who is it?
누구입니까?
He didn't say
그는 말하지 않았다
That person is weird
그 사람 이상해요
But he left an address for you
그런데 그 사람이 너한테 주소를 남겼어
address
주소
why don't you tell me
왜 나한테 말하지 그래?
You were trying on a kimono just now
당신은 지금 기모노를 입어보고 있었습니다.
It's not yet six o'clock
아직 여섯시가 안됐는데
you hurt me
너는 날 아프게한다
Why is my watch slow?
내 시계가 느린 이유는 무엇입니까?
Could it be when you were just trying on clothes?
그냥 옷을 입어봤을 때였을까요?
I accidentally touched the watch crown
실수로 시계 용두를 만졌는데
cold dew
차가운 이슬
address
주소
I wrote down the address on the note.
메모장에 주소를 적어두었어요.
Where is the note?
메모는 어디에 있나요?
Don't yell at me
나에게 소리 지르지 마세요
you yell at me
당신은 나에게 소리를 지르다
so I
그래서 나는
I can't even remember it
기억도 안나는데
think carefully
잘 생각 해봐
I
나
I put it in my bag
가방에 넣었어요
I'll find it
내가 찾아볼게
here
여기
where exactly
정확히 어디에
I
나
How could it not be?
어떻게 그럴 수 없습니까?
Here it is
여기있어
The address is here
주소는 여기입니다
I clearly remember
나는 분명히 기억한다
etc.
등.
I just discussed it with Zuo Shuangtao
방금 Zuo Shuangtao와 논의했습니다.
Since it’s a Japanese wedding
일본 결혼식이니까
You should wear the most traditional pure white kimono
가장 전통적인 순백색 기모노를 입어야 합니다.
Look at this set
이 세트 좀 보세요
cold dew
차가운 이슬
I'm looking forward to you wearing Bai Wuguan's look
바이우관의 룩을 입으시길 기대합니다
But I have something very important now
그런데 지금 아주 중요한 일이 있어요
Have to leave right away
바로 떠나야 해
You are not allowed to leave
당신은 떠날 수 없습니다
If you don’t accompany me to try on this kimono,
저와 함께 이 기모노를 입어보지 않으신다면,
I won’t get married like this
나 이런식으로 결혼 안할래
Miss Hanlu
미스 한루
How long does it take to get to Sanguantang Road?
삼관탕루까지 가는데 시간이 얼마나 걸리나요?
five minutes
5분
quick
빠른
Are you OK
괜찮으세요
how long will it take
얼마나 걸릴까요
Just turn at the intersection ahead.
바로 앞에 있는 교차로에서 방향을 틀면 됩니다.
Hurry up
서둘러요
Could it be
그럴 수 있을까?
I'm still destined to be a concierge after all.
결국 나는 여전히 컨시어지가 될 운명이다.
Reflective
반사
Glass
유리
glass reflective
유리 반사
sorry
죄송합니다
I didn't do well enough today
오늘은 별로 잘 못 했어
you did good enough
넌 충분히 잘했어
I'm worried about you now
난 지금 당신이 걱정돼요
There is an old fox at the foot of the mountain
산기슭에 늙은 여우가 있어요
I know how to deal with him
나는 그 사람을 어떻게 대해야 할지 알아요
Today I
오늘 나는
While helping you change clothes
옷 갈아입는 걸 도와주면서
I saw a lot of injuries on your body
네 몸에 상처가 많이 난 걸 봤어
Does he often abuse you?
그 사람이 당신을 자주 학대하나요?
Yamashita is really a devil
야마시타는 정말 악마야
It's too painful for you to continue like this
계속 이러는 건 너무 괴로워
You should leave him as soon as possible
가능한 한 빨리 그 사람을 떠나야 해
Leave Shanghai
상하이를 떠나다
After I'm done I think
다 마친 후에 생각하면
I should finish things before
그 전에 일을 끝내야 해
I will not leave
나는 떠나지 않을 것이다
But you are walking on thin ice by doing this
그런데 이렇게 하면 살얼음판 위를 걷고 있는 셈이다.
Just think of it as making a thriller movie
그냥 스릴러 영화를 만든다고 생각하세요
I have played love roles
나는 사랑의 역할을 해왔습니다.
comedy
코메디
There are also costumes
의상도 있어요
I haven’t made a thriller movie yet.
저는 아직 스릴러 영화를 만들지 않았어요.
like robin hood
로빈후드처럼
It’s fun to think about it
생각만 해도 재미있네요
You have to promise me
나한테 약속해야 해
You and Chen Jiaping
당신과 천자핑(Chen Jiaping)
We must be together happily
우리는 행복하게 함께 있어야 해
Never leave each other
절대 서로 떠나지 마세요
I can no longer be happy
난 더 이상 행복할 수 없어
So as long as I see you can be happy
그러니까 내가 보기만 하면 넌 행복할 수 있어
It's a kind of satisfaction
일종의 만족감이죠
What did you say
뭐라고 하셨나요
The recipe is not in the phone booth on Sanguantang Road
삼관탕로 전화부스에는 레시피가 없습니다.
right
오른쪽
Behind this phone
이 전화기 뒤에
Just such a button
딱 그런 버튼이네
Then inside this button
그런 다음 이 버튼 안에
Is there any mystery?
미스터리가 있나요?
I've checked everything
다 확인했어요
Nothing at all
전혀 아무것도
Just an ordinary button
그냥 평범한 버튼
This is not a button
이것은 버튼이 아닙니다.
It's cufflinks
커프스 단추예요
cufflinks
커프스 링크
Will the formula be taken away by Yamashita in advance?
야마시타가 미리 공식을 빼앗아 갈까요?
Nope
아니요
I saw with my own eyes that Yamashita arrived later than me.
야마시타가 나보다 늦게 도착한 것을 나는 내 눈으로 보았다.
That means Luo Guanqun deceived Shanxia
즉 Luo Guanqun이 Shanxia를 속였다는 의미입니다.
I think it's impossible
불가능하다고 생각해요
If Luo Guanqun wants to deceive Shanxia
Luo Guanqun이 Shanxia를 속이고 싶다면
Then he can run away completely after getting the gold bars.
그러면 금괴를 획득한 후 완전히 도망칠 수 있습니다.
Why do you have to wait until six o'clock to call?
왜 전화하려면 6시까지 기다려야 합니까?
There's no need
필요없어
So what's going on?
그래서 무슨 일이야?
I don't know either
나도 모르겠어요
This is so weird
이건 정말 이상해
Think about it again
다시 생각해 보세요
But anyway
하지만 어쨌든
You did a great job today
오늘 정말 훌륭한 일을 하셨습니다
And cold dew
그리고 차가운 이슬
Just didn't expect it
단지 예상하지 못했을 뿐이지
Our first real collaboration
우리의 첫 번째 진정한 협업
It failed
실패했다
This matter is not over yet
이 문제는 아직 끝나지 않았습니다
Yamashita didn't get the formula
야마시타는 공식을 이해하지 못했습니다
He won't give up either
그 사람도 포기하지 않을 거야
The same to you
너도 마찬가지야
Not careful at all
전혀 조심하지 않음
The injury from last time hasn’t healed yet
저번 부상은 아직 낫지 않았는데
Injured again this time
이번에도 부상을 당했다
I'm out of iodine. I'll buy some iodine.
요오드가 부족해요. 요오드를 좀 사겠습니다.
forget it
잊어 버려
This pharmacy is closed
이 약국은 문을 닫았습니다
let's talk tomorrow
내일 이야기하자
my office
내 사무실
tincture of iodine
요오드 팅크
I'll go with you
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것이다
Just don't go
그냥 가지 마세요
stay well
잘있어
I'll be back soon
곧 돌아올거야
Pay attention to safety
안전에 주의하세요
forty five
사십 오
forty six
마흔 여섯
Kobayashi
고바야시
get off work
퇴근하다
Is there anyone else upstairs?
위층에 다른 사람은 없나요?
There's no one left, everyone's gone
남은 사람도 없고 모두가 떠났어요
good
좋은
Is there anyone else upstairs?
위층에 다른 사람은 없나요?
The lady has arrived
아주머니가 도착했어요
Give
주다
Thanks
감사해요
Chief Uchida
우치다 소장
Whenever you subscribe to Liangyou Magazine
Liangyou Magazine을 구독할 때마다
and
그리고
Office with glass countertop
유리 조리대가 있는 사무실
There are eight rooms in total
방은 총 8개 있어요
but
하지만
With this kind of structure
이런 구조로
There is only Manager Luo’s room
루오 매니저님 방만 있어요
I can confirm now
이제 확인할 수 있어요
this picture
이 사진
It was taken in Manager Luo's office
루오 매니저 사무실에서 촬영되었습니다
So I conclude
그래서 나는 결론을 내린다
This letter to Mr. Yamashita
야마시타 씨에게 보내는 이 편지
It must be Manager Luo
루오 매니저겠지
Or it was sent by one of his men.
아니면 그의 부하 중 한 명이 보낸 것입니다.
The formula must also be in the hands of Manager Luo
공식은 Luo 관리자의 손에도 있어야 합니다.
Jiaping
자핑
eat some fruit
과일 좀 먹어
Luo Guanqun
루오관쿤
He's finished
그는 끝났어
What's the meaning
무슨 뜻인가요?
Uchida already knows
우치다는 이미 알고 있다
The person who traded with Yamashita was Luo Guanqun
야마시타와 거래한 사람은 나관춘(羅관춘)이다.
how did he know
그 사람은 어떻게 알았지?
He arranged for Qian Xiucai to secretly investigate the matter
그는 Qian Xiucai에게 이 문제를 비밀리에 조사하도록 주선했습니다.
When I just got you medicine
방금 약을 받았을 때
I happened to hear Qian Xiucai reporting to Uchida.
우연히 Qian Xiucai가 Uchida에게 보고하는 것을 들었습니다.
If Luo Guanqun collapses,
나관춘이 무너지면
Then we're all screwed
그럼 우리 다 망한 거야
Uchida also said
우치다도 말했다.
Luo Guanqun and his men must be cut into pieces
Luo Guanqun과 그의 부하들은 산산조각이 나야합니다
We need to evacuate quickly
빨리 대피해야 해요
No more thinking
더 이상 생각하지 마세요
no
아니요
Why
왜
Has Luo Guanqun got any clues?
Luo Guanqun은 어떤 단서를 얻었습니까?
Put it in this phone booth
이 전화부스에 넣어두세요
Only he knows this
이 사실은 그 사람만이 알죠
And only he has a clue to the formula
그리고 오직 그 사람만이 공식에 대한 단서를 가지고 있어요
We ran away at this time
우리는 이때 도망쳤다
All the clues are broken
모든 단서가 깨졌습니다.
What are you going to do?
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
coming
오는
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
Ruined
망가진
What's over
무슨 일이야?
Uchida already knows
우치다는 이미 알고 있다
You were the one who traded with Takeo Yamashita
야마시타 타케오와 거래한 사람은 당신이었군요
Shuyun
슈윤
You avoid it
당신은 그것을 피
I have something to do with Jia Ping
나는 Jia Ping과 관련이 있습니다
It's Jia Ping who's here
여기 와 있는 사람은 Jia Ping이에요
sister in law
시누이
Then you guys talk first
그럼 너희들이 먼저 얘기해봐
how did he know
그 사람은 어떻게 알았지?
Uchida arranges for Qian Xiucai
Uchida는 Qian Xiucai를 준비합니다.
Investigate this matter secretly
이 문제를 비밀리에 조사하라
Qian Xiucai found the remake recipe in the photo
Qian Xiucai는 사진에서 리메이크 레시피를 찾았습니다
reflected glass
반사유리
Taken in your office
사무실에서 촬영
Qian Xiucai
치안 슈카이
This bastard
이 새끼야
Don't look at others as harmless animals
남을 무해한 동물로 보지 마세요
In fact, it is harboring evil intentions
사실은 나쁜 의도를 품고 있는 거다.
Ambitious
거창한
Then how did you know?
그럼 어떻게 알았어?
Zuo Shuangtao went to the store to help me get medicine.
Zuo Shuangtao는 내가 약을 구하는 것을 돕기 위해 가게에 갔다.
Just look at your room lights on
방 불이 켜져 있는 걸 좀 봐
She went over to see what was going on
그녀는 무슨 일인지 보려고 다가갔어
I just heard the two of them talking.
방금 두 사람의 대화를 들었습니다.
you
너
And all your people
그리고 당신의 모든 사람들
Cut them all off
다 잘라버려
Lao Luo
라오루오
We can't stay in the trading house anymore.
우리는 더 이상 교역소에 머물 수 없습니다.
only run
오직 달리다
The only way to save your life is to run
목숨을 구하는 유일한 방법은 도망치는 것뿐이다
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
let me see
좀 보자
What are you thinking about?
당신은 무엇에 대한 생각?
Don't you have a hiding place?
숨을 곳은 없나요?
This place of business
이 사업장은
The secret is deep and the disaster is deep
비밀은 깊고 재앙도 깊다
I thought there would be such a day
그런 날이 있을 줄 알았는데
But I didn't expect it to be so sudden
하지만 이렇게 갑작스러울 줄은 몰랐어
And you
당신은요
what to do
무엇을 해야할지
Zuo Shuangtao's aunt found a place for us
Zuo Shuangtao의 이모가 우리를 위해 자리를 찾았습니다
Hide for a while
잠시 숨어보세요
good
좋은
Jiaping
자핑
Tired you up
피곤해
Don't even think about dragging me down in vain.
나를 헛되이 끌어내릴 생각은 하지도 마세요.
Where is my gold bar?
내 골드바는 어디에 있나요?
She doesn't know this
그녀는 이것을 모른다
I let the big spoon
큰 스푼을 줬어요
Take Shuyun there first
슈윤을 먼저 거기로 데려가세요
I'll clean it up
내가 청소할게
I'll clean it up with you
내가 너랑 같이 청소할게
Then I'll send you there
그럼 내가 거기로 보내줄게
You can't trust me
당신은 나를 믿을 수 없습니다
Yes or no
예 혹은 아니오
If it's Uchida
우치다라면
You pretend you don't know anything
넌 아무것도 모르는 척 해
Hello
안녕하세요
Chief Uchida
우치다 소장
now go
이제 가
Is there a problem
문제가 있습니까
OK OK
그래 그래
How to say
말하는 방법
Let me go to the gendarmerie headquarters
헌병대 본부로 가자
Talk about an emergency meeting
긴급회의에 대해 이야기해 보세요
There's no going back, Lao Luo
돌아갈 수 없어, 라오루오
Mrs. Luo
루오 부인
do not worry
걱정 하지마
That place is still safe
그 곳은 아직 안전해
Where are we going?
우리는 어디로 가는 걸까요?
longwuli
롱우리
Number three hundred and fifteen
번호 315
Do something for the Japanese?
일본인을 위해 뭔가를 하시나요?
Sooner or later it will end like this
조만간 이렇게 끝나겠죠
Fortunately, Manager Luo is really foresighted.
다행스럽게도 Luo 감독은 정말 선견지명이 있습니다.
The road to Hong Kong has long been paved
홍콩으로 가는 길은 오랫동안 포장되어 있었다
When has it been?
언제였나요?
Still caring about your wife so much
아직도 아내를 너무 걱정하고 계시네요
Very affectionate between children
아이들 사이에는 매우 다정한
From then on fell to the end of the world
그때부터 세상 끝까지 떨어졌다
Only Shuyun can accompany me.
오직 슈윤만이 나와 동행할 수 있다.
And you
당신은요
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
I
나
Go to Yan'an
옌안으로 가다
What
무엇
Neither the Japanese nor the Chinese army will let me go.
일본군도, 중국군도 나를 놓아주지 않을 것이다.
I can only go to Yan'an and join the Communist Party
나는 옌안에 가서 공산당에 가입할 수밖에 없습니다.
Looks a lot like the Communist Party
공산당이랑 많이 닮았네
correct
옳은
Why did Zuo Shuangtao hear Uchida say
Zuo Shuangtao는 왜 Uchida의 말을 들었습니까?
Yamashita didn't get the formula at all.
야마시타는 공식을 전혀 이해하지 못했습니다.
impossible
불가능한
I'll make the recipe
레시피는 내가 만들어줄게
I put it in the phone booth on Sanguantang Road.
Sanguantang Road의 전화 부스에 넣었습니다.
Sanguantang telephone booth
삼관탕 전화부스
Isn’t it Xiafei Road?
샤페이 로드 아닌가요?
That was used to test you
그건 당신을 시험하는 데 사용됐어요
Zhao An took the blame for the Five of Hearts
Zhao An은 Five of Hearts의 책임을 맡았습니다.
The Five of Hearts is still in the store.
Five of Hearts는 아직 매장에 있습니다.
It was Damasao's idea
다마사오의 생각이었어
It really has nothing to do with me
정말 나랑은 상관없는 일이야
OK OK OK
오케이 오케이 오케이
How do you relieve your anger?
분노를 어떻게 해소합니까?
All right
괜찮은
Anyway
그래도
our time is over
우리 시간은 끝났어
I ask you
나는 당신에게 묻습니다
Why didn't Yamashita get the formula?
야마시타는 왜 공식을 얻지 못했나요?
how could I know
내가 어떻게 알아
You don’t know who knows?
당신은 모르나요? 누가 알겠어요?
Why are you so concerned about the formula?
왜 공식에 그렇게 관심을 두나요?
You can’t really be a communist, right?
당신은 정말 공산주의자가 될 수 없겠죠?
You are talking nonsense
넌 말도 안되는 소리를 하고 있구나
I'm having a good time working in a business firm
나는 회사에서 즐거운 시간을 보내고 있어요
Not because of you
너 때문이 아니야
I've become a street rat now
난 이제 길거리 쥐가 됐어
You don't give people Yamashita's formula
사람들에게 야마시타의 공식을 알려주지 마세요.
That's why Yamashita was angry about it
그래서 야마시타는 화를 냈어요
You caught too many gold bars
금괴를 너무 많이 잡았어요
enough
충분한
What should I do
어떻게 해야 하나요?
What should I do with Zuo Shuangtao?
Zuo Shuangtao를 어떻게 해야 하나요?
what are you going to do
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
patrol
순찰
Scared me
날 무섭게했다
Did you hide the recipe?
레시피를 숨겼나요?
Do you still have a chance to make another fortune?
아직 또 다른 부를 벌 수 있는 기회가 있나요?
I don't
나는 아니에요
Luo Guanqun
루오관쿤
Now I think about eating alone
이제 혼자 밥먹을 생각이 나네
right
오른쪽
I swear
맹세해요
I really don't
난 정말 그렇지 않아
I tell you
나는 당신에게 말한다
Why don't you tell me the truth
왜 나에게 진실을 말해주지 않니?
The patrol is right next to it.
순찰대가 바로 옆에 있습니다.
I stepped on the accelerator and drove over
액셀을 밟고 차를 몰았어
Neither of us can escape
우리 둘 다 탈출할 수 없어
OK OK OK
오케이 오케이 오케이
I really swear to you
정말 맹세해요
I don't
나는 아니에요
If I lie to you
내가 당신에게 거짓말을 한다면
Let my wife cuckold me again
내 아내가 다시 나를 속이게 놔두세요
Okay
좋아요
Then when will you
그럼 언제 할래?
Hidden this recipe in the phone booth
이 레시피를 전화부스에 숨겼어요
last night
지난 밤
Went alone
혼자 갔다
one person
한 사람
No one follows
아무도 따라오지 않아
No
아니요
Mrs. Luo here
루오 부인이 여기 있어요
Slow down a little
조금 천천히
It's not easy to walk
걷기가 쉽지 않네요
Can't the car drive in?
차가 들어갈 수는 없나요?
Can't get in here?
여기 들어갈 수는 없나요?
Got here
저기로가
Why does it smell so bad here?
여기서는 왜 이렇게 냄새가 좋지?
We are on the run now
우리는 지금 달리고 있어요
Mrs. Luo
루오 부인
I originally thought I could get both cash and goods.
처음에는 현금과 물품을 모두 받을 수 있다고 생각했어요.
I thought it was quite beautiful
꽤 예쁘다고 생각했는데
I don’t want to provoke the devil Yamashita either.
나도 악마 야마시타를 자극하고 싶지 않다.
Why don't you tell me not to give him the formula?
그에게 공식을 주지 말라고 나한테 말해보는 게 어때?
This is not a button
이것은 버튼이 아닙니다.
It's cufflinks
커프스 단추예요